<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<reviews>

  <item>
    <img fileName="tjs_mazzanoble_01.jpg" orientation="landscape" />
    <description>
     <![CDATA[<p>You have no idea what kind of ambiance can be created with flowers until you have seen Teressa's work in action. It goes above and beyond your typical centerpieces. Teressa sees "art" in everything. She uses wood, fabric, tree branches, fruit... the world is one, big, beautiful floral arrangement if you see it through Teressa's eyes.</p>
      <p>I feel truly blessed to have worked with Teressa. While I thought our venue was beautiful and decorated wonderfully, Teressa's work was hands down the star of the show (and that's coming from the bride, mind you!)</p>
      <p>I managed to hold it together all day-- didn't cry when I put my dress on for the first time, saw my parents, or the groom. But when I walked into the venue and saw the work Teressa did, I totally lost it. I couldn't have dreamed it better. Every one of the 13 tables had a different centerpiece yet everything tied together perfectly. I wish I could take credit for this but alas, I barely gave her any direction other than our colors (orange and pink), my affinity for dahlias, and a few photos I saw where oranges were used in centerpieces. She totally took it and ran. Above and beyond anything I imagined. Our guests are still talking about how beautiful the tables looked. </p>
      <p>Professionally Teressa is a dream. Very professional, organized and quick to respond to emails. She was insanely patient with us as we seemingly added and deleted items from the list. All of our vendors commented on how wonderful she was to work with. </p>]]>
    </description>
    <client name="Bart + Shelly"/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <img fileName="tjs_machado_01.jpg" orientation="landscape" />
    <description>
      <![CDATA[<p>Teressa is a one of a kind floral designer and artist. She is creative, kind, visionary and goes above and beyond. Teressa puts her all into your event and it shows - my flowers and decor were beyond gorgeous and were exactly what I have always imagined. Teressa's ability to envision how different fabrics, textures and colors work together creates a style unlike any other. I guarantee your wedding will be unique, perfectly you and more spectacular than anything you've ever seen on Pinterest. I am so, so happy to have chosen Teressa as my florist and event designer and highly recommend Teressa Johnson Studio.</p>]]>
    </description>
    <client name="Claire + Landon"/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <img fileName="tjs_holden_01.jpg" orientation="landscape" />
    <description>
      <![CDATA[<p>We cannot thank you enough for all of your hard work with the flowers for our wedding.  They were absolutely beautiful.  Thank you for being flexible and changing some things around when we needed, You were a joy to work with, and I am so lucky that I could trust you with the look of our wedding!  You are amazing!</p>]]>
    </description>
    <client name="Brian + Emily"/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <img fileName="tjs_didericksen_01.jpg" orientation="landscape" />
    <description>
      <![CDATA[<p>Ryan and Teressa- Wow!  You guys did a fantastic job with all of the flowers and set up!  I feel like a lot of things came up the week of and you guys took on so much for me that I can’t thank you enough!  I loved my flowers and the reception space was exactly what I had hoped for.  Everything was just picture perfect and you gave me such peace of mind for the big day.  We love you guys.  Thank you so much!</p>]]>
    </description>
    <client name="Tyler + Cassie"/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <img fileName="tjs_bell_01.jpg" orientation="landscape" />
    <description>
      <![CDATA[<p>Our experience working with Teressa was delightful in every way. The flowers Teressa chose and designed were exquisite in every detail. The service was exceptional. She accommodated some special requests by the bride. The flowers at the wedding were a highlight of a very special day!</p>]]>
    </description>
    <client name="Stephen + Brett"/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <img fileName="tjs_howe_01.jpg" orientation="landscape" />
    <description>
      <![CDATA[<p>Teressa Johnson Studio was FANTASTIC to work with. From the first meeting to the day of the wedding, we knew that we chose the right company for our wedding. Teressa is fun, thoughtful, super organized, and incredibly creative. It's two days after my wedding and I'm taking a honeymoon break to write this review because she was THAT GREAT. </p>
      <p>And, the flowers? The design? Flawless, timeless, gorgeous. She understood our style and our budget and matched both with grace. She made the process fun and inviting, and I never worried about any of the details. It is absolutely worth going with the best when it comes to these parts of your wedding and Teressa Johnson Studio is that: the best!</p>]]>
    </description>
    <client name="Brain + Michelle"/>
  </item>
  <item>
    <img fileName="tjs_jefferies_01.jpg" orientation="landscape" />
    <description>
      <![CDATA[<p>I was astounded by her work. The flowers and decorations at my wedding were absolutely beautiful!! I gave her very little direction in what I wanted her to do, just told her the flowers I didn't want and the color scheme I wanted, and what she came up with was absolutely perfect. Her artistic abilities in flower arranging are beautiful. I got a lot of comments on how beautiful my wedding was decorated. I would recommend her to anyone!</p>]]>
    </description>
    <client name="TJ + Beth"/>
  </item>
   
</reviews>
